Privacy Policy – Magical Brands                                                                                                               [Skip to content](#MainContent)

Your cart is empty
------------------

Have an account?

[Log in](https://magicalbutter.com/customer_authentication/redirect?locale=en&region_country=US) to check out faster.

### Your cart

FREE SHIPPING FOR ORDERS $75+

Add to get freeshipping

$0 $75

Loading...

### Subtotal

$0.00

Taxes and [shipping](https://magicalbutter.com/policies/shipping-policy) calculated at checkout

Update

Complete Checkout

[Holiday Sale! | Buy 1 Gummy Maker, Get 1 Free! | Save automatically at Cart (Must have 2 in cart)](https://magicalbutter.com/collections/bundle-deals)

    Bundle Deals

    Shop

        Kitchenware

        Ingredients

        Merch

    Gummies

    Recipes

    Community

        Learn

* Currency
    
    Currency
    
    * USD $

Privacy Policy
==============

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or social security number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

**To personalize your experience**  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

**To improve our website**  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

**To improve customer service**  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

**To process transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

**To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**

**To send periodic emails**  
**The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.**

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?  
**Yes, cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.

Cookie Settings

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
**We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [https://www.magicalbutter.com/page/terms-and-conditions](https://www.magicalbutter.com/page/terms-and-conditions)

Your Consent  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy  
**If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

The below companies may collect personal information when you interact with our digital property, including IP addresses, digital identifiers, information about your web browsing and app usage and how you interact with our properties and ads for a variety of purposes, such as personalization of offers or advertisements, analytics about how you engage with websites or ads and other commercial purposes. For more information about the collection, use and sale of your personal data and your rights, please use the below links.

[https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy/](https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy/)

[https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-rightsrequest-form/](https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-rightsrequest-form/)

Contacting Us  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.magicalbutter.com

_[support@magicalbutter.com](mailto:support@magicalbutter.com)_

_**800-420-4334**_

MB World Headquarters
---------------------

+

E-Mail: [support@magicalbutter.com](mailto:support@magical.com "Email Us")

Phone: [+1 (800) 420-4334](tel:00118004204334)

Shop
----

+

Info
----

+

Legal
-----

+

### Join Our Magical Community

Stay Highly Informed
--------------------

Exclusive deals, new products, infused recipes, & more

 Submit

© 2024, [Magical Brands](https://magicalbutter.com/). Public Benefit Corp. Website by [Future Holidays](https://futureholidays.co/)

Payment methods

* American Express
* Apple Pay
* Diners Club
* Discover
* Mastercard
* PayPal
* Shop Pay
* Venmo
* Visa

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.
